In this world...
Is the destiny of mankind controlled by some transcendental entity or law?
Is it like the hand of God hovering above?
At least it is true...
...that man has no control, even over his own will.
Some danger always lies in the act of hunting...
...despite the fact it is an imperial event.
You never know what kind of
beasts hide within the woods...
What are you trying to say?
Of course, not only are
the beasts dangerous...
...but so are the stray arrows that may
have been launched at the beasts.
A stray arrow?
And a nastily-poisoned stray arrow at that...
If you mean...
A stray arrow, General.
Feel no shame about shape
Weather changes their phrase
Even mother will show you another way
So put your glasses on
Nothing will be wrong
There's no blame. There's no fame
It's up to you
The first words should be found
Whatever holds you back
I...
...can...
I can get it off
Tell me what...
Tell me what you want
I don't know why...
Don't know why...
Don't know why you're afraid
Tell me what...
Tell me what you'd say
I don't know why...
Don't know why...
Too late...
It's too late
Assassination
Well, it seems they cannot
catch the quarry easily.
Would Your Majesty like
to pursue the quarry with them?
No, I would not.
I'm not as young as I used to be...
...and I'm afraid of earning their
displeasure when I carry off...
...what they've pursued for two hours.
It is very kind of Your Majesty.
Look out! It's running into the brush!
Well done, kid!
There's no use getting sore!
I don't get sore!
Your feelings are written all over your face.
Why do we have to watch
those nobles play around?
It's ridiculous!
We've got no choice.
This is our duty too.
Besides, this is easier to deal
with than fighting on some battlefield.
That's true!
There's no need to worry about being killed.
I like swinging my sword
in battle. It's my nature.
Oh man, can you think of
anything more complicated than that?
Corkus, you again...
Shut up!
Listen!
It's a very important honor...
Formally, the only escorts for
the fall hunt were the White Dragons...
...the best knights in the regular army!
In other words, we were
singled out and granted the privilege!
We've had to run back
and forth in battle for years...
...to reach this point and win real status.
But you...
How dare you call this ridiculous?
If you love wielding your
sword so much, suit yourself!
Do you dislike hunting?
W-Well...
I...
This is my first time going hunting.
My father compelled me to go with him...
...but I do not think I should
like such a thing as hunting.
It is cruel...
So is war...
Why do most men commit to such
affairs that only produce bloodshed?
Oh my!
Hold it like so,
then place it softly to your lips.
That swollen-headed...
Your Grace...
Do not fuss.
We will surely have a better opportunity.
We had best wait for
a chance when he is alone.
There it goes!
Drive it into the corner!
Don't let it get away!
Pursue it!
My lady!
Hey, look!
Whoa, whoa!
Whoa!
Have you hurt yourself, my lady?
We're all right, aren't we?
My lady...
What is the matter?
I was scared, very scared!
My heart is still beating so fast.
I have never ridden a horse
so fast before in all my life.
I can see that it's taken
your mind off things, at least.
Griffith!
Shall we go back, my lady?
Everyone must be worried about you.
Griffith!
Captain, Captain!
Are you all right?
Griffith, are you all right?
Hold on!
Captain, hold on!
Griffith!
Hey, Princess!
What's this all about?
Where the hell
did this arrow come from?
From where?
You're hurting me!
Leave me alone!
I-I do not know... I do not...
Not good...
The arrow might have pierced his heart.
No way!
That arrow was well-poisoned with
the extract of the deadly calagile bean.
Even a scratch will let the poison
into his blood and send him to hell.
Griffith!
Do not panic.
Captain!
Hey!
Are you really okay?
It must be...
...poisoned for sure.
And a deadly poison as well...
So how come?
This is why.
This served as my shield.
The Egg of the King!
It's that...
...necklace you always wear.
How can it be?
Can it really be true?
Wow, it's really a miracle...
It's more like the devil's
own luck than a miracle.
Yeah, that must be like
a talisman against evil.
The devil's luck...
That was some kind of luck...
It's amazing!
Griffith, remove your armor just in case.
I have to see whether
you got injured or not.
No need.
I'm totally fine.
No way!
It was poisoned, wasn't it?
What if you got a scratch
and the worst should happen?
Believe me. I am fine.
I escaped without
a scratch on my body.
But if...
E-Excuse me...
I am sorry.
This happened only because
I could not handle a horse...
That is not a concern, my lady.
It is our duty to guard you.
Who in the world intended
to kill our captain anyway?
Wait, could he have been
aiming at the princess?
We can't let this go either way!
Let's kill him!
I'll search the brush
around here with my men.
Come on, get moving!
It is quite expensive.
This poison, I mean.
How shameful!
I sincerely apologize, but...
I have no ears for your excuses!
The affair has been
settled for the present...
It's assumed Tudor's assassins
were aiming for the princess's life.
We are virtually immune to suspicion.
On the other hand, our actions...
...gave Griffith credit for guarding
the princess's life with his own body.
All the commoners began talking of
him as a hero once news got around!
Even His Majesty is very grateful!
Ultimately, we have helped
him increase his status!
What a shameful situation!
But the arrow could never
have perfectly struck his chest...
...if the assassin was really
aiming at the princess.
What do you think
I should do? Go and explain...
...to His Majesty that we were merely
trying to assassinate Griffith?
On top of all this, he's still
alive, as you well know!
All things considered,
that was most unlikely to happen...
Enough!
Leave!
His eyes...
He looked as if he had power over me...
As if I was a trifling thing
to be held in contempt...
That look was in his eyes.
Nonsense!
I am royalty!
I even have a claim to the throne!
Regarding my status and class...
...I am worlds apart from
that man of common birth.
Nevertheless...
I've seen that look before...
For a moment, his eyes seemed
to be a beast's focusing on prey...
Yes!
He gazed at me the way
a hawk would gaze at prey...
Is it because...
No, that cannot be.
There were many
other feudal lords nearby.
I just met his gaze for a moment...
Firstly, there was no evidence of it...
He couldn't...
Hey...
Thanks for coming.
Can you wait a moment?
I'll finish up everything soon.
It keeps on growing.
Have you read them all?
Well, yes, almost.
When you become so distinguished,
you must do more than battle.
Well, I really just read
them out of mere curiosity.
History, religion,
philosophy, chemistry, tactics...
There is even a book on applying
makeup and a book on cooking...
...there are so many...
So what's the problem?
I want to ask you to kill a man for me.
Kill a man?
Who?
The man who is next in line
to the throne of Midland...
...the general of the White Dragons, Count Julius.
The reason...
...is this!
This arrow was poisoned with the
essence of the deadly calagile bean.
No ordinary person would
ever have a use for such a bean.
Only one man has purchased
this deadly poison recently...
He is the best archer in the
White Dragons, a man named Hail.
I paid off an attendant
to help smell out the plot.
She reported that she saw that
man come out of Julius's office...
...this evening, right after he got
a good scolding from the general.
This is an assassination.
It could not be more
different than fighting in battle.
It's a dirty task, and failure will never be allowed.
You must not be seen either.
On account of the difficulty, I am
asking if you would undertake the task.
Will you undertake it for me?
This is not like you.
You should just order me to do it,
without saying all this other crap.
Looking back, the morning comes.
Don't find your face in your glass.
Take the moonlight by the tail.
It's a rainy sight. You're shading.
What is that?
It's just the same.
What is trying your crown?
I'm spending my glass, walking back.
So wear my glass. You're fading.
I'm waiting so long.
I'm waiting...